

NGUYỄN THANH TUẨN ANH

JUNIOR .NET DEVELOPER



Apply experience in coding skills and understanding of the market to become a professional fullstack developer, bringing a lot of value to customers. Thereby helping the Company increase the number of customers and expand the customer base.

WORK EXPERIENCE

08/2018 - 08/2022

Software engineering

University of Economics and Finance UEF

- -Ability to lead small teams during college.
- -Knowledge current frameworks.

09/2022 - Now

EximBank

Emloyee

- -Build Api for partner.
- -Create websites for internal units to use.
- -Maintain and participate in the development of available projects.

04/2022 - 07/2022

TMA Solutions

Intern

- -Learn knowlege to become fullstack developer.
- -Create project individual to improve skill.



Số điện thoại

0962411810



tuananhnguyenthanh521@gmail.com



Địa chỉ

Email

Quận 10,TPHCM



Ngày sinh

02/03/2000



Giới tính

Nam



EDUCATION

University of Economics and Finance UEF | 08/2018 - 08/2022

SOFTWARE TECHNOLOGY

Graduated



SKILLS

Office Information Technology

- Proficient in using Word, Excel, Power Point

Back-end

- C#,.Net core, MVC, WebAPI
- -Restful API, Spring Framework

Front end

- -HTML, CSS, JS, Tailwindcss.
- -REACTJS, VueJs, Nextjs.

Other

- -SQLServer, Mysql, Mongodb
- -Git.
- -SOLID, Agile, Scrum.



Certificate

2022

English B1

© topcv.vn